import React from "react";

export const Email = "d19125334@mytudublin.ie";

export const consentItems = {
    "title": "User Consent Form",
    "items":[
        "I confirm that my email address is correct.",
        "I confirm that I am over 18.",
        "I confirm that my data could be anonymous.",
        "I consent to taking part in this research.",
        "I consent that my data will be stored securely and achieved.",
        "I consent that my data could be used for our research purposes.",
        "I consent that my data could be used for dissemination purposes at academic conferences or publications.",
        "I understand that my data can be deleted by your request at any time.",
        "I understand that I can stop participating in this research project at any time.",
        "I agree to participate in a research project conducted by Na Li (d19125334) from TU Dublin in Dublin, Ireland."
    ]
}

export const reseachinfomation ={
    "title": "Experiment Information",
    "items":[
        {"question":"What is this research about?",
        "answer":"The purpose of this experiment is to explore users’ behaviours during a situated dialogue with a virtual avatar."},
        {"question":"Why are you doing this research?",
        "answer":"I am exploring to build a natural conversion in virtual avatar-human interaction (HAI) and Human-Robot Interaction (HRI). Exploring human’s behaviours in a situated dialogue is a first step of this research, dialogue planning for building a natural conversion between a virtual avatar and human is the second step of this research."},
        {"question":"Why have I been invited to take part?",
        "answer":"You can have a simple conversion in English with a virtual avatar who is over 18."},
        {"question":"What will happen if I decide to take part in this research study?",
        "answer":"If you decide to participate, you will be able to talk with the avatar in a video chat. You will be asked to assess this conversation and be able to give feedback about your interactions with the avatar."},
        {"question":"How will the data be used?",
        "answer":"Your conversation with the avatar will be recorded (video, audio). The recordings from the sentences you speak and your response from body language and facial expression will be saved for later analysis. Your replies in the questionnaires will be statistically evaluated along with all other participants of this study."},
        {"question":"How will you protect my privacy?",
        "answer":"You will choose a nickname which has no connection to your real name. In the study you will be referred to only by the basic demographic information you provide,  age group and gender."},
        {"question":"How is this research funded?",
        "answer":"This project is funded by SFI Centre for Research Training in Machine Learning (MLLabs)."},
        {"question":"What are the benefits of taking part in this research study?",
        "answer":"You may find it is enjoyable to interact with an avatar who responds to your speech."},
        {"question":"What are the risks of taking part in this research study?",
        "answer":"If you see negative expressions and unreasonable responses from the avatar, you may feel bad. When using the speech recognition, it may be frustrating to get a different result from what you expect. The video recordings of your conversation with the avatar are identifiable."},
        {"question":"What happens if I do not want to take part or if I change my mind? ",
        "answer":"It is up to you to decide whether or not to take part. You can do that by clicking the “Signup” or “Signin” button on the experiment website. You can change your mind anytime and withdraw with no disadvantage. If you do decide to take part, you will be asked to read and keep this information sheet. What’s more, you will be asked to tick a circle to confirm consent. You are free to withdraw from the experiment at any time without giving a reason and without detriment to yourself. If you wish to withdraw, you can send an email to d19125334@mytudublin.ie with the subject ”withdraw from experiment. If you want a copy of your data, or wish your data to be deleted, you can state that in the email and I will follow your request."},
        {"question":"What about the video recordings?",
        "answer":"An essential part of my research is to record your interaction with the avatar. You should be comfortable with the recording process at all times and are free to stop recording at any time."},
        {"question":"Who has reviewed the research project?",
        "answer":"This project has been reviewed and approved by the Research Ethics Committee at TU Dublin."},
        {"question":"How will I find out what happens with this project?",
        "answer":"This research is part of my PhD project. The results will be published and become part of my thesis. If you want to know more, please contact Na Li, email d19125334@mytudublin.ie."}
    ]
}


